我從哪來？
Where I come from?
舞女們眾說紛紜
Witch will say it differently.
翻譯:一葉障目
我朝著水晶走過去的時候，我想知道為啥我會在這。
As I walk towards to the crystal, I quiver thinking about why I was here.
每隔幾年，精靈女性舞者就會發情。
Every few years, elven women performer right sexual maturity.
時軸:晚風
我們進入一個傳送門，不管后面是什么，上去就干。
We entered a portal and fulfill our desires with whatever lies beyond.
壓制:雪夜
和我們做愛的總是不同的東西
Who were made with us was never the same.
我們這樣做因為我們想感謝大自然
We do this because it also appreciates naturalist.
不管是什么形式
No matter what form it is.
I was so intent
但是，我的欲望告訴我
Yet, with my sound restless desire
我很想被干。
I knew I want this badly.
我碰了一下水晶，然后消失在一束光里。
I touch the crystal and disappeared into a light
本字幕由夜桜字幕組制作
射精結束之后，我發現自己有一種滿足感
With the written finished，I found satisfied in mooding
自那天開始我就屈服了...
I yield for the day I entered..